servicelocator.org 2003-06-02

# Locator- Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the America's Service Locator website and reviewing our privacy policy. At America's Service Locator (ASL) and the U.S. Department of Labor (USDOL), your privacy is a matter of the highest priority. Consequently, America's Service Locator has been designed to make the vast majority of its information and services available without the user having to provide any private information. In addition, ASL does not use "cookies" or any other techniques to collect information about you without your personal knowledge. However, some private information is collected for statistical purposes and, under certain circumstances, the user may volunteer private information in order to access special features and products in ASL.

 **Statistical Information**

The ASL policy governing statistical information is as follows:

  * Any private statistical information collected by ASL will be limited to non-personal information that is used to identify user preferences and make program enhancements.

  * Specifically this information includes your Internet domain, type of browser, type of operating system, the date and time of your visit to the website, specific pages you visited, and the previous website that you visited if it was linked to ASL.

**E-Mail Correspondence and Inquiries**

If for some reason, you decide to send ASL or the Service Center an e-mail message, it will normally contain your return e-mail address. Please be advised that if you ask us to address a specific question and include any personal identifying information, we may elect with your permission to share that information with other federal offices or agencies in order to obtain the appropriate response. These federal agencies are governed by the Privacy Act of 1974 and will handle your private information in accordance with the restrictions contained in that Act. If you use e-mail to correspond to ASL, it is important to understand that e-mail is not always secure from interception. Consequently, if you are sending very sensitive or personal information, you may wish instead to contact us through the Postal Service at: 

  * CareerOneStop Service Center  
55 E. Fifth Street  
102 Fifth Street Center  
St.Paul, MN 55101  
Toll Free Telephone: 1 (877) 348-0502   

**Links to Other Sites**

Our web site has links to other federal agencies and private organizations. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.
